# Eng./Mina Anwer Lewes

### **Contact Information:**

Address: 513, Port Said Street, Ghamra Avenue, Cairo.

Mobile: 0020 - 122- 192 - 6646.

E-mail: minaanwer05@gmail.com.

minaanwer06@gmail.com.

## **Professional Summary:**

Strongly skilled and experienced C# Dot Net Developer with vast knowledge Of a variety of computer languages. Adept at all aspects of web, desktop, and Mobile development, Able to know how for any challenge.

# **Career Objective:**

To be a professional Dot net developer and utilize my technical Knowledge through contribution in multiple valuable projects. seeking also to be Experienced Dot net Instructor with many contributions in Development community.

#### **Education:**

Oct. 2016 To June 2017	9 Month Diploma of professional web and business intelligence, System Development track, information Technology Institute (ITI). Course work URL: <a href="www.iti.gov.eg">www.iti.gov.eg</a>
Sept. 2008 To June 2013	Bachelor of Electric Engineering Communication and Electronics Department Faculty of Engineering Assuit University, Assuit, Egypt. Cumulative Grade: Good. Graduation Project Title: CBTC system ("Communication Based Train Control System").

Graduation Project Grade: Excellent.

Sept. 2008 Certificate of High School from Eldeware high school, Assuit, Egypt.

Relevant Experience:

May 2012

Rolovani axpononeo i			
June 2016 until now	Dot net developer at EBC (Egyptian Banking Company )		
Aug.2015 To Sept. 2016	Light current software Engineer, at Hurb Trade company.		
Mars 201 <i>5</i> To June 201 <i>5</i>	Technical Support Engineer at Raya.		

# **Training:**

Mars 2013 PLC training at Siemens Lap Asuit University.

June 2012 in Asuit Railway Station.

June 2011 in Asuit Power Steam Station.

### **Courses Given:**

Introduction To OOP. (available online via my YouTube Channel).

Private C Sharp Course. (two level)

### **Skills:**

Language: English: Good in Written and Spoken English.

Dutch : Acceptable.

Arabic: mother tongue.

Highlights:

Excellent presentation skills.

Able to explain technical information in everyday language.

Effective communication skills.

Expert-level knowledge of C# programming and SQL. Good incorporation of training materials and media.

Uses hands-on training approaches to make the material easier to learn.

Strong understanding of best training practices.

## **Certificates:**

April 2017 IBM cloud Bluemix Certification.

Sept. 2012 Gent Certification For Fire Alarm Systems.

### **Personal Information:**

Nationality Egyptian.

Date of birth 7/12/1989.

Marital life Single.

Linked in Profile https://www.linkedin.com/in/mina-anwer-427959123/

YouTube channel <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCgpedLPpZU Xx9gpK4p1PjQ">https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCgpedLPpZU Xx9gpK4p1PjQ</a>

References and Documents available up on request.